Finding Aid for Democratic Party of Michigan records, 1932-2008
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Detroit Office Topical Files
  - 1960-1968
    - Democratic National Convention 1968 (Box 78)
    - Democratic State Central Committee
      - Biennial report (by Z. Ferency) 1967 (Box 78)
      - Budget 1967 (Box 78)
      - Budget 1968 (Box 78)
      - Financial Committee (and financial reports 1967) (Box 78)
      - Minutes (Box 78)
      - Resolutions 1968 (Box 78)
    - Legislative Information for Teamwork (LIFT)
      - Manuals (Box 78)
      - Newsletters (and related) 1965-1966 (Box 78)
    - Legislative Programs 1963, 1965 (Box 78)
    - Michigan Federation of Democratic Women (Box 78)
    - Mid-west Conference 1967 (Box 78)
    - Public Relations 1967-1968 (Box 78)
    - Register and Vote Committee (Box 78)
    - Registration Drive 1967 (Box 78)
    - State Convention 1968 (Box 78)
    - Tax Bill (Box 78)
    - Voter Identification and Registration 1967-1968 (Box 78)
    - Women's Day
      - 1960-1964, 4 folders (Box 78)
      - 1965-1968, 3 folders (Box 79)
    - Young Democrats (Box 79)
  - 1969
    - Correspondence (Box 79)
    - Democratic State Central Committee
      - ABM (anti-) Committee (Box 79)
      - Budget (Box 79)
      - Business and Professional Associations (Box 79)
      - McNeely, James (Box 79)
      - Membership Reports (Box 79)
      - Minutes (Box 79)
      - Press releases (Box 79)
      - Resolutions (Box 79)
    - Housing (Box 79)
    - Mid-West Conference (Box 79)
    - New Democratic Coalition of Michigan (Box 79)
    - Political Reform Federation (Box 79)
    - Scullion, Mary Kay (Box 79)
    - Teen Democrats (Box 79)
    - Wayne County Committee (Box 79)
    - Wayne County Federation of Democratic Women (Box 79)
    - Young Democrats (Box 79)
  - 1970
    - Correspondence (Box 79)
    - Democratic State Central Committee
      - Consumer Action Program (Box 79)
      - Finance (Box 79)
      - Goals for 1970 (Box 79)
      - Jeffrey, Mildred (Box 79)
      - Leadership Report (Box 79)
      - Levin's Law (Box 79)
      - McNeely, James (Box 79)
      - Press releases (Box 79)
      - Register and Vote (Box 79)
    - Equal Rights for Women (Box 79)
    - Jefferson-Jackson Day (Box 79)
    - Political Reform Commission Convention (Box 79)
    - Teen Democrats (Box 79)
    - Wayne County Federation of Democratic Women (Box 79)
    - Women's Activities (Box 79)
  - 1971
    - Miscellaneous (Box 79)
  - 1972
    - Best Petition Drive (Box 80)
    - Campaign materials
      - General (Box 80)
      - Education Candidates (Box 80)
      - Kelley Campaign (Box 80)
      - Schedules (Box 80)
    - Democratic Party-Michigan (History) (Box 80)
    - Legislative newsletters (Box 80)
    - Michigan Democratic Black Caucus (Box 80)
    - People's Lib (Box 80)
    - Precinct Delegate Selection (Box 80)
    - Presidential Primary (Box 80)
    - Taxes (Box 80)
    - Wayne County Democrat (Box 80)
    - Women (miscellaneous) (Box 80)
    - Women's Caucus (Box 80)
  - 1974
    - Budget (Box 80)
    - Campaign
      - Manual (Box 80)
      - General (Box 80)
    - Candidates (Box 80)
    - Charter Commission (Box 80)
    - Charter Symposium (Box 80)
    - Convention (August) (Box 80)
    - Correspondence (Box 80)
    - Guidelines (Box 80)
    - Leadership newsletter (Box 80)
    - Press releases (Box 80)
    - Resolutions (Box 80)
    - Winograd, Morley (Box 80)
  - 1975
    - Affirmative Action Plan (Box 80)
    - Budget (Box 80)
    - Convention (Box 80)
    - Correspondence (Box 80)
    - Leadership Retreat (Box 80)
    - Lists (Box 80)
    - Maynard, Libby (Box 80)
    - Membership (Box 80)
    - Press releases (Box 80)
    - Rules and Political Reform (Box 80)
    - Women (Box 80)
  - 1977
    - Convention February 1977 (Box 80)
    - Con-Con (Box 80)
    - Membership (Box 80)
    - Policy Committee (Box 80)
    - President's Club (Box 80)
    - Resolutions (Box 80)
  - 1978
    - Affirmative Action Committee (Box 80)
    - Appeals Committee (Box 80)
    - Budget (Box 80)
    - Correspondence (Box 80)
    - Finance Committee (Box 80)
    - Guidelines (Box 80)
    - Leadership newsletter (Box 80)
    - Policy Committee (Box 80)
    - Resolutions (Box 80)
    - Structure (organizational) (Box 80)
  - 1980-1982
    - Correspondence (Box 81)
    - Campaign plans (Box 81)
    - Human Rights and Social Welfare subcommittee (Box 81)
    - Leadership newsletter (Box 81)
    - Oakland County Platform (Box 81)
    - Officers meeting (Box 81)
    - Policy Committee, 2 folders (Box 81)
    - Precinct delegates (Box 81)
    - Press releases (Box 81)
    - State Central Committee meetings (Box 81)
    - State Convention 1980 (Box 81)
    - State Convention 1981 (Box 81)
- Topical Files and additions 1971-1983
  The Topical Files series includes various materials sent to the party's offices and filed for future reference. There is some original material but also newsletters, clippings, brochures, reports, etc.
  - Association of State Democratic Chairs 1979-1983 (Box 82)
  - Democratic National Committee
    - Bylaws 1979-1981 (Box 82)
    - Compliance Review Commission 1979-1980 (Box 82)
  - Dollars For Democrats 1979-1982 (Box 82)
  - Federal Appointments
    - General 1977-1980 (Box 82)
    - Judge, Eastern District 1977-1979 (Box 82)
    - Judge, Western District 1977-1978 (Box 82)
  - Federal Election Commission 1977-1979 (Box 82)
  - Meetings
    - Leadership Committee, State Central Committee (Box 82)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 82)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 82)
  - Membership Disclosure Lists 1973-1974 (Box 83)
  - Memos, Letters 1973-1974 (Box 83)
  - Millionaires Party 1980, 1982 (Box 83)
  - Policy Committee
    - Agricultural Subcommittee 1981-1983 (Box 83)
    - Economy Subcommittee 1981-1982 (Box 83)
    - International Relations Subcommittee 1981-1982 (Box 83)
  - Public Act 388
    - General 1977-1978 (Box 83)
    - Advisory Opinions 1977-1979 (Box 83)
  - Undated
    - Biographies (miscellaneous) (Box 83)
    - Party Publications (Box 83)
    - Rules (Box 83)
  - 1976
    - Campaigns (Box 83)
    - Literature (Box 83)
    - Supreme Court (Box 83)
    - Udall, Mo (Box 83)
    - Voter Registration and Get-Out-The-Vote (Box 83)
    - Conventions (Box 83)
    - Democratic National Convention, Delegate Selection (Box 83)
    - Precinct Delegates (Box 83)
  - 1977
    - Federal Appointments, U.S. District Attorney, Western District of Michigan (Box 83)
  - 1978
    - Get-Out-The-Vote (GOTV) (Box 83)
  - 1979
    - Democratic National Committee, Congressional Campaign Committee (Box 83)
    - Leadership Newsletters (miscellaneous issues) (Box 83)
    - Public Act 388 Amendments (Box 83)
    - Screening Committee (Box 83)
    - Voter Identification (Box 83)
  - 1980
    - Campaigns (Box 83)
    - Democratic National Convention (Box 83)
    - General (Box 83)
    - Delegate Selection Plan (Box 83)
    - Site Selection (Box 83)
    - Precinct Delegates (Box 83)
  - 1981
    - Democratic National Committee, Platform Accountability Committee (Box 84)
    - Economic Advisory Council (Box 84)
    - Membership Drive (solicitation committee) (Box 84)
    - Policy Committee, Subcommittee (Box 84)
    - Redistricting Project (expense sheets), 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Rules and Political Reform Committee (Box 84)
  - 1982
    - Campaigns (Box 84)
    - Analysis (Box 84)
    - Results (Box 84)
    - Democratic National Committee (Box 84)
    - Meetings, State Central Committee (Box 84)
  - 1983
    - Blanchard, James (Box 84)
    - Conventions (Box 84)
    - County Party Newsletter (Box 84)
    - Democratic National Committee (Box 84)
    - Edelson, Howard, Field Representative (Box 84)
    - Executive Director (Box 84)
    - Mastin, Philip, Recall (Box 84)
    - Meetings (Box 84)
    - Leadership (Box 84)
    - State Central Committee (Box 84)
    - Michigan Young Democrats (Box 84)
    - Levin, Carl (Box 84)
    - Policy Committee (Box 84)
    - General (Box 84)
    - Agricultural Subcommittee (Box 84)
    - Energy and Natural Resources Subcommittee (Box 84)
    - Human Rights and Social Welfare Subcommittee (Box 84)
    - State, Cities, and Counties Policy Subcommittee (Box 84)
  - 1984
    - Democratic National Convention (Box 84)
    - Mondale, Walter (Box 84)
  - Administrative
    - Calendars 1986 (Box 85)
    - Democratic State Central Committee 1983-1987 (Box 85)
    - Hart/Kennedy House Inc. 1986 (Box 85)
    - Higher Education Task Force 1982 (Box 85)
    - Leadership Meeting Minutes 1982 (Box 85)
    - Party Accountability Task Force 1979 (Box 85)
    - Personnel Practices 1980-1981 (Box 85)
  - Computer Database
    - 1983 (Box 85)
    - 1985 (Box 85)
    - 1986, 2 folders (Box 85)
  - Fundraising
    - Administrative 1986 (Box 85)
    - Correspondence 1983 (Box 85)
    - Direct Mail Program 1986 (Box 85)
    - Donors 1978-1986 (Box 85)
    - Mailings 1986-1987 (Box 85)
  - Organizations
    - Central Michigan University 1981 (Box 85)
    - Michigan State University 1978-1983 (Box 85)
    - Michigan Education Association 1981-1982 (Box 85)
    - State Board of Education 1980-1983 (Box 85)
    - University of Michigan 1979-1983 (Box 85)
    - Wayne State University 1979-1981 (Box 85)
  - Policy Committee
    - 1977-1978 (Box 85)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 85)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 85)
  - Publicity
    - Resolutions (undated) (Box 85)
    - Policy 1981 (Box 85)
    - Press Releases 1980-1983, 2 folders (Box 85)
  - Congressional Districts 1973-1986
    - First 1977-1982 (Box 85)
    - Second 1981-1983 (Box 85)
    - Third 1976-1983 (Box 85)
    - Fourth 1977-1986 (Box 85)
    - Fifth 1976-1983 (Box 85)
    - Sixth 1977-1981 (Box 85)
    - Seventh 1981-1982 (Box 85)
    - Eighth 1977-1986 (Box 85)
    - Ninth 1977-1983 (Box 85)
    - Tenth 1977-1981 (Box 85)
    - Eleventh 1973-1986 (Box 85)
    - Twelfth 1978-1983 (Box 85)
    - Thirteenth 1979-1982, 2 folders (Box 85)
    - Fourteenth 1977-1984 (Box 85)
    - Fifteenth 1977-1986 (Box 85)
    - Sixteenth 1977-1983 (Box 85)
    - Seventeenth 1973-1982, 2 folders (Box 85)
    - Eighteenth 1979-1982 (Box 85)
  - Campaigns and Elections 1972-1986
    - Election Analysis
      - 1978 (Box 86)
      - 1980 (Box 86)
    - GOTV (Get Out The Vote) Plan 1976-1980 (Box 86)
    - National
      - Congress
        - Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee 1986 (Box 86)
        - Financial 1986 (Box 86)
        - Results 1986 (unofficial) (Box 86)
      - President
        - 1972, 1976 Elections (Box 86)
        - Convention Delegates (Box 86)
        - 1980 Election
          - Caucus Results (unofficial), 2 folders (Box 86)
          - Caucus System Guidelines (Box 86)
          - Convention Delegates (Box 86)
          - Issues 1979 (Box 86)
        - Dukes Forum on Presidential Nominations 1981 (Box 86)
        - 1984 Election
          - Convention Delegate Selection Plan (Box 86)
          - Convention Site Selection Plan (Box 86)
        - 1988 Election
          - Lee Iococca 1986 (Box 86)
    - State
      - Courts Results 1986 (unofficial) (Box 86)
      - Financial Reports 1986 (Box 86)
      - Governor (Box 86)
      - Recall Election 1983 (Box 86)
      - Television 1983 (Box 86)
      - Advertising 1986 (Box 86)
      - Financial 1986 (Box 86)
      - Leadership Workshop 1986 (Box 86)
      - Press 1986 (Box 86)
      - Primary Results 1986 (unofficial) (Box 86)
      - Strategy 1986 (Box 86)
      - Legislature (Box 86)
      - Correspondence 1983 (Box 86)
      - Advertising 1986 (Box 86)
      - Financial 1986 (Box 86)
      - Results 1986 (unofficial) (Box 86)
    - Polling
      - 1980 (Box 86)
      - 1982 (Box 86)
      - 1983 (Box 86)
      - 1986 (Box 86)
  - Patronage 1979-1986
    - Correspondence 1979-1983, 2 folders (Box 86)
    - Governor's Appointments
      - 1983 (Box 86)
      - 1986 (Box 86)
    - Screening Committee 1980 (Box 86)
  - Campaigns and Elections 1972-1986 (Box 86)
  - Legislation 1976-1986
    - Campaign Finance 1985 (Box 86)
    - Federal Election Laws 1976 (Box 86)
    - Laws Relating to Elections 1980 (Box 86)
    - Michigan Election Law Amendments 1986 (Box 86)
    - Recodification of Election Laws 1986 (Box 86)
    - Summary of Election Laws 1986 (Box 86)
    - Textile Import Quota 1985 (Box 86)
  - Litigation 1986
    - Brennan Suit 1986 Re: Supreme Court Nominations (Box 86)
    - Campaign Finance Violation 1986 (Box 86)
    - Chamber of Commerce Lawsuit 1986 Re: Campaign Finance Law, 3 folders (Box 86)
- State Central Committee Meeting Minutes
  The State Central Committee series includes minutes and other materials from the meetings of the SCC. This is an artificially created series drawn together from various other series. It is not complete and thus the researcher should examine the files of the State Chair and the Headquarters series for gaps.
  - 1985-1986, 6 folders (Box 87)
  - 1987-1988, 2 folders (Box 87)
  - 1989-1990, 7 folders (Box 87)
  - 1991-1993 (multiple folders) (Box 87)
- State Convention files
  The State Convention series relates to meetings of the convention. Included are materials relating to the program, resolutions, platform, and rules of the party. Again, the researcher should examine the State Chair and Headquarters series to fill in gaps in the documentation. There is some material relating to the participation of the state party in the national convention.
  - 1968 (Grand Rapids)
    - Miscellaneous information, 5 folders (Box 88)
    - Credentials committee 1968 (Box 88)
    - New caucus meeting (Box 88)
  - 1969 (Detroit)
    - General (Box 88)
    - Credentials Committee (Box 88)
    - Program (Box 88)
    - Resolutions (Box 88)
    - Rules (Box 88)
  - 1970 (Grand Rapids)
    - General file (Box 88)
    - Candidates (Box 88)
    - Committees of the convention (Box 88)
    - Political reform commission (Box 88)
    - Resolutions/platform (Box 88)
  - February 1971 (Grand Rapids)
    - General file (Box 88)
    - Credentials Committee (Box 88)
    - Convention mailing instructions (Box 88)
    - Democratic State Central Committee members (Box 88)
    - District officers (Box 88)
    - Plenary session (Box 88)
    - Resolutions (Box 88)
    - Rules Committee (Box 88)
    - State Central meeting February 14, 1971 (Box 88)
    - Thank yous (Box 88)
  - 1972
    - General, 1 folders (Box 88)
    - County Resolutions June 1972, 4 folders (Box 88)
    - Farmers (Box 88)
  - 1973 (Detroit) General (Box 89)
  - 1984
    - Credentials Committee report (Box 89)
    - Platform (Box 89)
    - Resolutions (County) (Box 89)
    - Rules Committee report (Box 89)
    - State Convention, Detroit August 25-26, 1984 (Box 89)
  - 1985
    - Executive Committee selection (Box 89)
    - Platform Committee (Box 89)
    - Resolutions (Box 89)
    - Rules, proposed (State Democratic Convention) (Box 89)
    - Rules Committee (Box 89)
    - State Convention, Detroit February 9-10, 1985 (Box 89)
  - 1986
    - Correspondence (received) (Box 89)
    - Leadership (party), 2 folders (Box 89)
    - Membership letter (Box 89)
    - Policy Committee reports, 2 folders (Box 89)
    - Precinct delegate information (Box 89)
    - Press releases (Box 89)
    - Primary guidelines (proposed) (Box 89)
    - Project 500 (Box 89)
    - Rules (proposed) (Box 89)
    - Rules Committee report (proposed) (Box 89)
    - Voting, proportional (Box 89)
  - 1987
    - Contracts (Box 89)
    - Correspondence (received) (Box 89)
    - Leadership meetings, 2 folders (Box 89)
    - Membership letter and cards (Box 89)
    - O'Donnell, Tom (Box 89)
    - Policy Committee (Box 89)
    - Presidential Caucus Sites (County) (Box 89)
    - Press releases (Box 89)
    - Raffle (Box 89)
    - Staebler, Neil (Box 89)
    - State Convention (Rules Committee) (Box 89)
    - Subcommittee reports (Box 89)
    - Training program (Box 89)
  - 1988
    - Correspondence (received) (Box 89)
    - Delegate selection plan for 1988 (Box 89)
      (includes 1984 plan)
    - HB 4773 and SB 349 (Box 89)
    - Irwin, Mitch (Box 89)
    - Jacobetti resolution (Box 89)
    - Jefferson-Jackson Day dinner (Box 89)
    - Michigan Democrat (Box 89)
    - Neuner, Dennis (Box 89)
    - Presidential campaign (computer) (Box 89)
    - Presidential candidates and contacts (Box 89)
    - Press releases (Box 89)
    - Republican National Lawyers Association (1988 convention) (Box 89)
    - State Caucuses (primary) (Box 89)
    - State convention (Box 89)
    - Voter registration (Box 89)
  - 1982
    - Convention Call (Box 90)
    - Information Sheet (Box 90)
  - 1983
    - County and District Conventions (Box 90)
    - General (Box 90)
    - Proportional Voting (Box 90)
  - 1984
    - Convention Call (Box 90)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 90)
    - Planning Meetings (Box 90)
    - Rules (Box 90)
    - Seating Chart (Box 90)
  - 1985
    - Convention Call (Box 90)
  - 1986
    - Benefit Auction (Box 90)
    - Convention Call (Box 90)
    - Convention Schedule (Box 90)
    - District Issues (Box 90)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 90)
  - 1987
    - Convention Call (Box 90)
  - 1988
    - Caucuses (Box 90)
    - Convention Arrangements (Box 90)
    - Convention Call (Box 90)
    - Convention Script/Schedule (Box 90)
    - County Chairs (Box 90)
    - District Issues and Caucuses (Box 90)
    - Election Certificates (Box 90)
    - General (Box 90)
    - Nominating Forms (Box 90)
    - Post-Convention Ratification (Box 90)
    - Proportional Voting (Box 90)
    - Rules (Box 90)
    - Seating Chart (Box 90)
    - Tally Sheets (Box 90)
  - 1989
    - Convention Agenda (Box 90)
    - Convention Call (Box 90)
    - Convention Hall: Pontchartrain Hotel (Box 90)
    - Convention Officers (Box 90)
    - County Conventions (Box 90)
    - Credentials Committee (Box 90)
    - Delegates (votes by county) (Box 90)
    - District Caucuses (Box 90)
    - Executive Committee (Box 90)
    - Permits/Leasing Agreements (Box 90)
    - Platform (Box 90)
    - Rules Committee (Box 90)
    - Special Caucuses (Box 90)
    - Tally Sheet (Box 90)
  - 1990
    - Amendments/State Voting (Box 90)
    - Affidavits (Box 90)
    - Benefit Auction (Box 90)
    - Convention Call (Box 90)
    - Convention Hall: Cobo Center (Box 90)
    - Convention Officers (Box 90)
    - Convention Forms (Box 90)
    - County/District Conventions (Box 90)
    - Credentials Committee (Box 90)
    - Delegates (Box 90)
    - General (Box 90)
    - Group Meeting Suite Requests (Box 90)
    - Nominating Forms (Box 90)
    - Nomination Certificates (Box 90)
    - Platform (Box 90)
    - Platform Committee (Box 90)
    - Promotional Information (Box 90)
    - Proportional Voting (Box 90)
    - Report (Box 90)
    - Resolutions (Box 90)
    - Rules Committee (Box 90)
    - Tally Sheets (Box 90)
  - 1996 (Box 90)
  - 1999-2002, 4 folders (Box 90)
  - 2008 (Box 90)
  - Participation in the Democratic National Convention 1996, 2000 (Box 90)
- Appeals Committee 1995
  The Appeals Committee series consists of records related to cases handled by this committee, which was created to have jurisdiction over matters of procedural fairness and observance of party rules and regulations of internal operations. Audio tapes of hearings are included.
  - Fourteenth and Fifteenth Districts, 15 folders (Box 99)
  - Oakland County, 2 folders (Box 99)
  - Hearings of the Committee for the Fourteenth and Fifteenth districts April 3, 1995, 10 audiocassettes (Box 99)
- Publications and miscellaneous
  - Published, manuals, unprocessed, etc.
    - County Leadership Handbook," DSCC publication 1975 (Box 91)
    - "Reference Book for Party Leaders," DSCC publication 1967 (Box 91)
    - "Reference Book for Democratic Chairmen," DSCC publication 1961 (Box 91)
    - "1974 Campaign Manual" DSCC publication 1974 (Box 91)
    - Miscellaneous campaign pamphlets (Box 91)
    - Party directories (scattered dates), 5 folders (Box 91)
    - History of Michigan Democratic Party (Box 91)
    - Ingham County Democratic Party in the 1970s (by Marie E. Kingdon) (Box 91)
    - 2008 miscellaneous (Box 91)
    - Jefferson Jackson Day miscellaneous 1999, 2002, 2006 (Box 91)
    - List of Officers and Members of DNC undated (Box 91)
    - Literature related to Governor Jennifer Granholm (Box 91)
    - Party Platform 1996 (Box 91)
    - Personnel Policies undated (Box 91)
    - Resolutions for Party Platform Undated (Box 91)
    - Right to Vote 2000 (Box 91)
- Visual Materials
  Visual Materials series consists of three subseries: Photographs, Motion Pictures, and Videotapes. Within the photographs there is a set of files that includes both photographs and background information on party candidates and officeholders. Many of the photographs are studio portraits, although for the major figures, such as John Swainson and G. Mennen Williams, there is a greater variety to the content of the photographs. In addition to photographs, the series also includes motion pictures used in various campaigns and videotapes of party meetings and television spots.
  - Photographs
    - Bayh, Birch (Box 92)
    - Candidates (Box 92)
    - Cavanagh, Jerome (Box 92)
    - Democratic National Convention 1976 (Box 92)
    - Gilmore, Horace (Box 92)
    - Groups (Box 92)
    - Hare, James (Box 92)
    - Individuals (Box 92)
    - Jefferson-Jackson Dinner, Detroit March 29, 1971 (Box 92)
    - Levin, Sander (Box 92)
    - Meeting, Westin Hotel, Detroit circa 1980 (Box 92)
    - Michigan State University-Voter registration (Box 92)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 92)
    - Mondale Visit circa 1982 (Box 92)
    - Moody, Blair, Jr. (Box 92)
    - Non-Michigan Politicians (Box 92)
    - Official Portraits (Box 92)
    - Personalities (includes some biographical data)
      - A-B (Box 92)
      - C-F (Box 92)
      - H-K (Box 92)
      - L-M (Box 92)
      - N-R (Box 92)
      - R-T (Box 92)
      - U-Z (Box 92)
    - State Central Committee Members (Box 92)
    - State Legislature (Box 92)
    - Stevens, Don (Box 92)
    - Supreme Court (Box 92)
    - Truman visit 1955 (Box 92)
    - United States Congress (Box 92)
    - Voting (Box 92)
    - Williams, G. Mennen (Box 92)
    - Winograd, Morley (Box 92)
    - Woolner, Sidney (Box 92)
    - Young, Coleman (Box 92)
  - Biographies / Photographs of Political Figures 1965-1975
    - General
      - Ferency, Zolton (Box 92)
      - Hertzburg, Stuart, DSCC Treasurer (Box 92)
      - Howe, Betty, Chairperson, Oakland Co. (Box 92)
      - Humphrey, Hubert (Box 92)
      - Jeff-Jack Day May 1965 (Box 92)
      - J.F.K. House, Democratic Headquarters (Box 92)
      - Kennedy, Edward (Box 92)
      - Lewand, Tom, Biography (Box 92)
      - McNeely, James M. (Box 92)
      - Tucker, Don, Chairperson, DSCC Finance Committee (Box 92)
      - Winograd, Morley (Box 92)
    - Justices--Michigan Supreme Court (Box 92)
    - Statewide Elected Officials
      - Atchison, Leon (Box 92)
      - Austin, Richard (Box 92)
      - Brown, Paul (Box 92)
      - Bruff, John (Box 92)
      - Dade, Malcolm (Box 92)
      - Edwards, George C. (Box 92)
      - Einhauser, Mike (Box 92)
      - Fraser, Douglas A. (Box 92)
      - Hart, Adelaide (Box 92)
      - Hart, Jane (Mrs. Philip A. Hart) (Box 92)
      - Hart, Philip (Box 92)
      - Hoffa, James P. (Box 92)
      - Jeffrey, Mildred (Box 92)
      - Kelley, Frank (Box 92)
      - McNamara, Patrick V. (Box 92)
      - Miller, Annetta (Box 92)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 92)
      - Nederlander, Robert (Box 92)
      - Power, Philip H. (Box 92)
      - Reuther, Walter P. (Box 92)
      - Roach, Tom (Box 92)
      - Roberts, Barbara (Box 92)
      - Salas, Gumecindo (Box 92)
      - Swainson, Alice (Box 92)
      - Swainson, John B. (Box 92)
      - Watanen, John (Box 93)
      - Williams, G. Mennen (Box 93)
      - Williams, Nancy (Box 93)
      - Woodcock, Leonard (Box 93)
    - State Senators
      - General (Box 93)
      - Brown, Basil (Box 93)